<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://min-guk.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://min-guk.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-06-19T14:41:06+00:00</updated><id>https://min-guk.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Minguk Choi, Master&apos;s Student at Dankook University in South Korea. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Useful Articles for Rebuttals</title><link href="https://min-guk.github.io/blog/2024/rebuttal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Useful Articles for Rebuttals"/><published>2024-05-23T01:14:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-23T01:14:00+00:00</updated><id>https://min-guk.github.io/blog/2024/rebuttal</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://min-guk.github.io/blog/2024/rebuttal/"><![CDATA[<p>This article is written for researchers who are experiencing difficulties in preparing and conducting their first rebuttal after submitting a paper to a conference, just like I did before. Last winter, I submitted a paper as the first author for the first time, and I felt great anxiety and helplessness while waiting for the upcoming rebuttal. To alleviate these feelings, I sought advice from those around me and searched the internet, but it was not easy to find a solution.</p> <p>Since the strategies or examples of rebuttals are generally not publicly available, so for junior researchers like me, this feels like a fear as dark as night. It is not easy to know what makes a good rebuttal letter, while you can gauge the quality of a paper by its citation count and the conference or journal in which it is published,</p> <p>Fortunately, in recent times, several senior researchers have recognized these difficulties and have written useful articles: 1) sharing their own rebuttal strategies, 2) analyzing and introducing the rebuttal processes of conferences, and 3) disclosing the their paper reviews. Through below articles, I was able to approach the rebuttal process more confidently and strategically.</p> <ul> <li>Rebuttal Strategies <ol> <li> <p><a href="https://people.cs.vt.edu/~danfeng/papers/Yao-Rebuttal-Howto.pdf">Yao, Danfeng Daphne. “Rebuttal How-to: Strategies, Tactics, and the Big Picture in Research.” (2023)</a>.</p> </li> <li> <p><a href="https://cs.stanford.edu/~merrie/merrie_rebuttal_tips.pdf">Morris, M. R. “My Rebuttal-Writing Process for HCI Venues.”</a></p> </li> </ol> </li> <li>Analyzing and Introducing Rebuttal Processes <ol> <li> <p><a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1751157723000524">Huang, Junjie, et al. “What makes a successful rebuttal in computer science conferences?: A perspective on social interaction.” (2023)</a></p> </li> <li> <p><a href="https://sigmodrecord.org/publications/sigmodRecord/1906/pdfs/07_Reports_Ailamaki.pdf">Anastasia Ailamak, et. al. “The SIGMOD 2019 Research Track Reviewing System” (2019)</a></p> </li> <li> <p><a href="https://mrl.snu.ac.kr/~jehee/SIGGRAPH_decision_process.pdf">Jehee Lee, “SIGGRAPH 논문은 어떻게 결정되는가 (KOR)”(2008)</a></p> </li> </ol> </li> <li>Disclosed Conference Papers and Reviews <ol> <li><a href="http://dbis.cs.tu-dortmund.de/cms/en/publications/2021/mxtasks/sigmod2021-reviews/index.html">Database (SIGMOD/VLDB) conference papers and reviews from the DBIS group at TU Dortmund</a></li> </ol> </li> </ul> <p>I hope this article will be helpful for those preparing for conference paper submissions and the rebuttal process.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="academic"/><category term="rebuttal"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is written for researchers who are experiencing difficulties in preparing and conducting their rebuttal, just like I did last winter.]]></summary></entry></feed>